mosaicglobe.com 2011-06-24

# MosaicGlobe artist websites - the best free art portfolio website for artists. - Privacy Statement

### 

### **Privacy Policy**

In the course of serving our clients, it is necessary for MosaicGlobe to acquire, store and transmit customer communications and information that our clients may regard as private or sensitive. Some information is provided by the client in order to establish service. Other data is generated and maintained by MosaicGlobe in the normal course of providing services. This Privacy Policy applies to all user data attained by MosaicGlobe and does not apply to any data collected by MosaicGlobe customers or any entities affiliated with MosaicGlobe. Use of MosaicGlobe services constitutes acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

**Your Personal Information**  
During the registration process a user is required to provide information such as name, email and billing data. This collected information is used to authenticate users and provide MosaicGlobe services. MosaicGlobe may at other times collect data from users in the form of online surveys in order to better understand our user’s needs and provide better services. 

The personal information we collect is not shared with or sold to any third party; except as necessary to complete a transaction in order to provide requested service(s) or; when required to comply by law* or; when MosaicGlobe has a good faith belief that the law requires the disclosure for illegal activities** on the part of the user. 

These exceptions include any electronic mail or other electronic communications that MosaicGlobe stores or transmits for its users. MosaicGlobe will not intentionally monitor private electronic mail messages sent or received by its users unless required to do so by law, governmental authority, or when public safety is at stake. MosaicGlobe may, however, monitor electronic mail systems electronically to insure satisfactory operations.

*MosaicGlobe may disclose information, including but not limited to, information concerning a user in order to comply with a court order, subpoena, summons, discovery request, warrant, statute, regulation, or governmental request. MosaicGlobe assumes no obligation to inform the user that their information has been provided and in some cases may be prohibited by law from giving such notice. 

**MosaicGlobe may disclose user information or information transmitted via its servers where necessary to protect MosaicGlobe and/or others from harm, or where such disclosure is necessary to ensure proper operation of the MosaicGlobe system. 

**General Information**  
MosaicGlobe will also track general server statistics such as (but not limited to) internet protocol (IP) addresses, referring/exit pages, visitor volume and patterns, peak traffic times, operating systems and browsers being used. This information will be used to analyze broad trends and server loads to prevent an interruption of services. This data may also be shared with third parties to show general service usage. This data is not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Your Data**  
MosaicGlobe operates the servers your site is hosted on and retains all rights to the MosaicGlobe application, however any information and images uploaded to your MosaicGlobe website remains your property. MosaicGlobe will make that data available to yourself and your visitors as long as you remain a client in good standing. Please refer to the ‘Terms of Service’ agreement to better understand your rights and responsibilities as a MosaicGlobe user. MosaicGlobe will not contact your mail list contacts and will not sell access to your site or site content for commercial gain. MosaicGlobe may share your site with others for promotional purposes.

**Your Security**  
MosaicGlobe takes every precaution to protect our user’s information. Collected data is protected by appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We utilize industry standard SSL-encryption to protect any sensitive user data submitted to MosaicGlobe. However, no medium of communication, including the Internet, is entirely secure and any information transferred to MosaicGlobe is done so at your own risk. Therefore, MosaicGlobe cannot be held responsible for loss, corruption or unauthorized acquisition and use of personal information transferred to our site, or for any damages resulting from such loss, corruption, unauthorized acquisition or unauthorized use. 

MosaicGlobe requires cookies to access your account. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from our server and is stored on your computer's hard drive. MosaicGlobe cookies are non permanent and expire after a short period of non-use.

MosaicGlobe users are assigned a user name and unique password which is required to access their account and personal data. It is the user's responsibility to protect the security of their user name and password. Users can change their password and personal data as the see fit.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection**  
MosaicGlobe does not target its services toward, and does not knowingly collect any personal information from users under 13 years of age.

**Future Changes to this Policy**  
This policy has been created with the understanding that changes may be required as Internet technologies and Internet business methods evolve. In the case of a business transaction, including but not limited to, a merger or sale of a portion of MosaicGlobe’s assets, customer information will likely be part of the assets transferred. Any and all changes to this Privacy policy will be posted to the website and users will be notified of the changes via a news update within their account settings page.
